discoverhongkong.com 2008-12-11

# DiscoverHongKong - Privacy Policy

You are welcome to discover all the information and entertainment of this Hong Kong Tourism Board Website.

This Privacy Policy has been developed in accordance with the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance (Chapter 486) of the Laws of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region of The People’s Republic of China. The Ordinance provides data subjects with rights to ascertain whether the Hong Kong Tourism Board holds personal data relating to them, to obtain a copy of that data, and to correct any data that is inaccurate.

Site visitors can freely explore this Website largely without having to reveal any personal data. On occasion however, it may be necessary for the Hong Kong Tourism Board to gather information on you for a specific purpose. We will always inform you when we are collecting such information. It is our intention to respect your request for privacy, and we try our best to provide you with communication channels to facilitate this. Once all gathered information has been used for the intended purpose, it is destroyed or de-identified.

The Hong Kong Tourism Board has created this statement in order to demonstrate its firm commitment to protecting your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering methods and dissemination practices for this Website. The Hong Kong Tourism Board is not responsible for the privacy practices of other linked sites. 

**Cookies**

The Hong Kong Tourism Board uses your IP address to assist in diagnosing problems with our server, and to administer our Website. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.

You can set your browser in order to be notified when you receive a cookie, offering the opportunity to decide whether you will accept it or not. Our site uses various types of forms for site visitors to request information and services, to enter contests, play games and to send e-mail messages of preferred pages. 

Advertisements displayed on our site may contain cookies. While cookies appear in other areas of our Website, those received via banner advertisements are collected by our advertising company and we do not have access to this information. Information collected by our advertising company will be governed by that company’s privacy policy.

**Use of your Personal Information**

The Hong Kong Tourism Board collects site visitors' contact information (such as an e-mail or street address) and demographic information (e.g. age, country of residence and travel history). This information is used by us to further our statutory objectives. Contact information from the forms is used to send promotional materials and information to you. If data collected is to be displayed at a later date, due care will be given to keep it anonymous and you will be advised in advance. Users may "opt-out" of receiving future mailings. Demographic information is used for our research requirements and to tailor your experience at our site, showing content of interest, and displaying the content according to your preferences. We may share with our advertisers such information on an aggregate basis. Users may “opt-out” of receiving future mailings.

When you come to our Website, our server software records the domain name of your computer. We may also track the pages you visit. We do these things so that we can measure traffic, gauge the popularity of various parts of the Website, gain some general knowledge about our audience and compile aggregated statistics.

Data collected by the Hong Kong Tourism Board is used only for the purposes indicated above. Personal information will not be disclosed to any third party except as follows:

  * On a confidential basis to agents we use in the ordinary course of our business, such as for data management and distribution of our promotional materials.  

  * As we may be required to do so by laws.  

  * As you indicate your choice to receive promotional materials from third parties named in the forms.

**Data Security**

The Hong Kong Tourism Board will take reasonable steps to ensure that all information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete, up-to-date and stored in a secure environment accessed only by authorized persons. However, we give no warranty against third parties hacking into the data or any unauthorised access to the data by anyone.

**"Opt-Out"**

You can opt-out from receiving information from the Hong Kong Tourism Board or to delete your information from our records at any time should you no longer wish to receive updates of Hong Kong Tourism Board developments, activities and promotions. To opt out, please enter your e-mail address below and click the submit button   

**Contacting the WebSite**

Should you have further questions regarding this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website and your interaction with it, or to request access and correction to your personal data, please contact: 

Manager - Web Management  
Hong Kong Tourism Board   
9-11 Floor, Citicorp Centre   
18 Whitfield Road  
North Point   
Hong Kong   
E-mail: [webmaster@discoverhongkong.com](mailto:webmaster@discoverhongkong.com), Fax: +852 2503 6103

| **PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTION STATEMENT**

The Hong Kong Tourism Board may from time to time collect your personal data specific for the purpose of event or activities organized or promoted by it ("Event").

**Purposes for which personal data are collected and used**

The Hong Kong Tourism Board may use the data collected and provided by you for one or more of the following purposes:

| 1. | To identify you for entry into lucky draw or any other promotional activities;  
---|---  
2. | To contact you regarding your enquiries, notify you of the results of lucky draw/ promotional activities and the subsequent presentation or redemption arrangement;  
3. | For announcement and publicity of lucky draw/ promotional activities' result;  
4. | For marketing and promotion purposes;  
5. | For identification and verification purposes;  
6. | For our own internal records, research and statistical purposes; and  
7. | For any other purpose pertaining to the Event.  
  
You are not required to provide the data. However, if you select not to supply the data as requested, your entry form or application form (as the case may be) will not be counted or processed or be eligible for the associated lucky draw/ promotional activities.

**Data Security**

The data you provide to us will be stored at the Hong Kong Tourism Board office or our server in Hong Kong accessible only to our authorised employees and contractors. However, we give no warranty against third parties hacking into the data or any unauthorised access to the data by anyone.

The Hong Kong Tourism Board will take reasonable steps to ensure that all information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete and up-to-date.

We may share your personal data with Event sponsors or authorised agents or contractors for prize presentation, redemption or delivery (as appropriate) in connection with the associated Event. By entering the competition or promotion, you acknowledge and expressly agree with the above. 

**Retention of Data**

We will keep your personal data only for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose for which it is being collected. We may also retain archived personal data for statistical purposes.

**Your Consent**

By submitting the requisite entry form/ application form, you certify that all information provided to the Hong Kong Tourism Board in the form is true and correct. You agree that your personal data given to and collected by the Hong Kong Tourism Board from time to time may be used and disclosed for the foregoing purposes, and to such persons as may be appropriate in accordance with this Personal Information Collection Statement and Privacy Policy of the Hong Kong Tourism Board. 

Please also refer to our Privacy Policy. 

_This Personal Information Collection Statement and our Privacy Policy are subject to change without prior or separate notification. Any changes will be posted to our Web site._
